(Penny:)He was supposed to meet you the other
day, but he kind of ended up in jail.
(Stan Lee:)I see. And you thought you'd just
come over to my house uninvited?
(Sheldon:)You said we were invited.
(Penny:)Oh, no, no. I said I'm inviting you
to come with me to Stan Lee's house.
You know, you fanboys are unbelievable.
(Stan Lee:)Do you think you can just ring
my doorbell anytime you want?
(Stan Lee:)I mean, why don't you just come on in
and watch the Lakers game with me?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not much of a sports fan,
but thank you.
(Penny:)I'm sorry.
He doesn't really understand sarcasm.
(Stan Lee:)Well, I'll give him something
he'll understand.
(Stan Lee:)-Joanie, call the police.
-Nice to meet you.
(Raj:)Fantastic Four, Daredevil...
(Raj:)...Invincible Iron Man,
Happy Hogan, Curt Connors--
(Howard:)Would you just let it go?
(Raj:)And worst of all, Fin Fang Foom.
-Hey. Where you been?
-I'll tell you where I've been.
(Sheldon:)You boys may have had gelato
with Stan Lee...
(Sheldon:)...and gotten autographed comics,
but I saw the inside of his house...
(Sheldon:)...and got an autographed application
for a restraining order.
(Penny:)Sweet.
(Sheldon:)Plus, I get to hang out with him again,
at the hearing.
(Sheldon:)This is going to look great...
(Sheldon:)...hanging next to my restraining order
from Leonard Nimoy.